<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-06-25T13:10:06+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">KLIC Hosts Collaborative Visit to Microsoft Research Asia in Hong Kong</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-collaborative-visit-to-microsoft-research-asia-in-hong-kong/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KLIC Hosts Collaborative Visit to Microsoft Research Asia in Hong Kong"/><published>2025-06-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-collaborative-visit-to-microsoft-research-asia-in-hong-kong</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-collaborative-visit-to-microsoft-research-asia-in-hong-kong/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624201033.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> On June 24, 2025, KLIC organized a collaborative visit to Microsoft Research Asia (MSRA) in Hong Kong, bringing together researchers, faculty, and students from City University of Hong Kong and MSRA for an afternoon of academic exchange and networking. <p><p/> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200442.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> The event began at 2:00 PM with a welcome speech by hosts Yan and Shengdong, followed by an overview of MSRA’s research direction, team structure, and institutional positioning, presented by Shujie and Yun. <p><p/> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200651.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200839.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200853.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> From 2:30 PM to 3:00 PM, Andong and Dingdong presented two ongoing research projects at MSRA Hong Kong, highlighting innovative approaches and recent findings. Their talks sparked engaging discussions and set the tone for deeper collaboration. <p><p/> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200124.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200612.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> Between 3:00 PM and 4:00 PM, representatives from CityU—including both faculty and students—shared their current research interests, challenges, and ideas for potential partnerships. This flexible session encouraged open dialogue and mutual learning. The visit continued with a guided tour of MSRA’s office space, offering guests a behind-the-scenes look at the institute’s working environment. The day concluded with a group photo session at 5:00 PM, marking the end of a productive and inspiring visit. This exchange not only strengthened ties between CityU and MSRA but also opened doors for future collaboration in HCI and related fields. </p></p></p></p></p></p></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 24, 2025, KLIC organized a collaborative visit to Microsoft Research Asia (MSRA) in Hong Kong, bringing together researchers, faculty, and students from City University of Hong Kong and MSRA for an afternoon of academic exchange and networking.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dr. Victor Leung Delivers Lecture at KLIC</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/dr-victor-leung-delivers-lecture-at-klic/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dr. Victor Leung Delivers Lecture at KLIC"/><published>2025-06-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/dr-victor-leung-delivers-lecture-at-klic</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/dr-victor-leung-delivers-lecture-at-klic/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250620212802.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> On June 20, 2025, Dr. Victor Leung, Assistant Professor at the School of Creative Media, City University of Hong Kong, gave a lecture at the Kowloon Interaction Center (KLIC) titled “My Journey of Exploration: From Computational Design to Digital Manufacturing and Robot Assembly”. <p><p/> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250620213222.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> Dr. Leung has taught at leading institutions including ETH Zurich, MIT, the University of Hong Kong, and Singapore University of Technology and Design, specializing in courses on computational design, digital manufacturing, and robot assembly. He has also led advanced workshops at international platforms such as the AA Visiting School and the ACADIA Conference. In addition to his academic work, Dr. Leung has collaborated with digital artists and architects to create dynamic installations, 3D-printed structures, and mechatronics projects. These works have been exhibited at international venues including the Venice Biennale and the Science Gallery in Melbourne, contributing to ongoing innovation in architecture, digital manufacturing, and robotics. KLIC thanks Dr. Leung for his visit and for sharing his experiences and expertise with the group. </p></p></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="Lecture"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Victor Leung Delivers Lecture at KLIC]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">HCI Summer School 2025 Begins at KMUTNB, Bangkok</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/hci-summer-school-2025/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="HCI Summer School 2025 Begins at KMUTNB, Bangkok"/><published>2025-06-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/hci-summer-school-2025</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/hci-summer-school-2025/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250618205144.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p>The <strong>HCI Summer School 2025</strong>, supported by <strong>ACM SIGCHI</strong>, is currently taking place at the <strong>Faculty of Information Technology and Digital Innovation, King Mongkut’s University of Technology North Bangkok (KMUTNB)</strong>. Scheduled from <strong>June 16 to 20</strong>, this five-day academic event brings together students, researchers, and guest speakers to explore foundational and emerging topics in Human-Computer Interaction (HCI).</p> <p>Participants arrived in Bangkok on June 16, with the program officially launching on June 17. The opening day featured a welcome speech by <strong>Asst. Prof. Dr. Dr.-Ing. Sunantha Sodsee</strong>, followed by an inspiring keynote from <strong>Prof. Shengdong Zhao</strong>. The day continued with lectures and workshops focused on identifying impactful research topics and brainstorming within the HCI domain.</p> <p></p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250618205131.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p></p> <p>Each day of the summer school is organized around a central theme:</p> <ul> <li><strong>June 18:</strong> Focus on Empirical Methods in HCI, including a research talk by <strong>Asst. Prof. Sanchari Das</strong>, a lecture on methodology, and a workshop on qualitative data collection.</li> <li><strong>June 19:</strong> Dedicated to Designing Technology for Health &amp; Wellbeing, featuring a talk by <strong>Asst. Prof. Yuhan Luo</strong> and a workshop on Human-AI interaction in health contexts.</li> <li><strong>June 20:</strong> Closing day with a research talk by <strong>Assoc. Prof. Tony Tang</strong>, a lecture on writing CHI papers, a workshop on research elevator pitches, and a panel discussion on the future of HCI in Asia.</li> </ul> <p>Held in Room 4A07 at KMUTNB, the summer school offers a rich blend of lectures, hands-on workshops, and collaborative discussions, fostering regional and international exchange in HCI research.</p> <p></p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250618205620.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="HCI"/><category term="summer"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[HCI Summer School 2025 Begins at KMUTNB, Bangkok]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Han Teng Presents on Visual-Touch Integrated Human-Machine Interaction</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/han-teng-talk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Han Teng Presents on Visual-Touch Integrated Human-Machine Interaction"/><published>2025-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/han-teng-talk</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/han-teng-talk/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250612201405.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p>On June 11, 2025, <strong>Han Teng</strong>, researcher at the <strong>Institute of Software, Chinese Academy of Sciences</strong>, delivered a talk titled <strong>“Visual-Touch Integrated Human-Machine Collaborative Interaction Platform.”</strong> The session introduced an innovative approach to multi-sensory interaction, with a focus on visual-touch fusion and its role in advancing human-machine-environment collaboration.</p> <p> </p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250612201353.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p> </p> <p>Abstract:</p> <p><em>Intelligent information technologies such as embodied intelligence and spatial intelligence promote the evolution of human-machine interaction towards complex spatial tasks, stimulate human instinctive needs for multi-channel perceptions such as vision, touch, and proprioception, and transcend the limitations of traditional screens. Visual-touch fusion is an interactive paradigm innovation driven by spatial task requirements, which helps the efficient and intelligent development of human-machine-environment collaboration. Its core lies in multidisciplinary cross-disciplinary research to address the perceptual and cognitive problems of visual-touch stimulation and the challenge of lagging development of tactile technology. The research team combined the model framework of cognitive processing and motion control, and expanded the multi-sensory feedback mechanism of vision, touch, etc. with sensory conflict and motion constraints as the main line, providing a theoretical basis for conducting research on the visual-touch fusion interaction paradigm. In view of the limitations of traditional tactile actuation technology, the research team developed a thin and light structure, high-efficiency, and high-temporal and spatial resolution electrotactile interface to expand its tactile rendering capabilities, and initially developed a visual-touch integrated human-machine collaborative interaction platform to serve important human-machine collaborative interaction fields such as embodied intelligence and remote operation.</em></p> <p><strong>About the Speaker:</strong> Han Teng is Deputy Director of the Human-Computer Interaction Laboratory at the Institute of Software, Chinese Academy of Sciences, and a National Excellent Young Scholar. He holds degrees from Xi’an Jiaotong University and the University of Manitoba, and has published nearly 40 papers in top venues such as CHI, UIST, and Nature Communications.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Talk"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Han Teng Presents on Visual-Touch Integrated Human-Machine Interaction]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">KLIC Session Shares Insights on Supervision Practices</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-session/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KLIC Session Shares Insights on Supervision Practices"/><published>2025-06-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-session</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-session/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250607164453.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p>On Friday, June 6, 2025, members of the Kowloon Interaction Center (KLIC) held a session focused on the topic of <strong>“Best Practice in Supervision.”</strong> The session was based on a workshop recently attended by one of the members, conducted by Imperial College London.</p> <p> </p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250607164443.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p> </p> <p>The discussion centered around approaches to supervising students, with an emphasis on reflecting on current practices and hearing diverse perspectives. In preparation for the session, participants were invited to share their thoughts anonymously through a survey, helping to create a more open and comfortable environment for discussion.</p> <p>The topic was relevant to both current supervisors and students who may take on supervisory roles in the future. By drawing from external insights and internal reflections, the session encouraged thoughtful dialogue within the group.</p> <p>KLIC thanks everyone who took part in the session and contributed to the conversation.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[KLIC Session Shares Insights on Supervision Practices]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MSRA Team Joins Student Presentation and Feedback Session</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/msra-team-joins-student-presentation-and-feedback-session/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MSRA Team Joins Student Presentation and Feedback Session"/><published>2025-06-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/msra-team-joins-student-presentation-and-feedback-session</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/msra-team-joins-student-presentation-and-feedback-session/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20250604105008.jpg" alt="" width="2000"/> </div> <p><br/> A group from Microsoft Research Asia (MSRA) recently joined a session featuring student presentations and feedback exchange. The event provided an opportunity for students to share their work and receive comments from experienced professionals in the field.</p> <p><strong>The MSRA attendees included:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Lily Sun, Director of the MSRA Accelerator Team</li> <li>Shujie Liu, Principal Researcher</li> <li>Beibei Shi, Principal Research Program Manager</li> <li>Jinglu Wang, Senior Researcher</li> <li>Yun Wang, Senior Researcher</li> </ul> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20250604105015.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p>During the session, several students presented their research ideas and ongoing projects. The MSRA visitors offered feedback, contributing their perspectives and engaging with the presenters.</p> <p>The session served as a valuable platform for interaction between students and researchers, encouraging thoughtful discussion and reflection. KLIC appreciates the participation of the MSRA team and the time they dedicated to engaging with the student work. <br/></p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20250604121741.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/></p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20250604121750.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/></p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20250604121757.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSRA Team Joins Student Presentation and Feedback Session]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">KLIC Members Share CHI 2026 Paper Ideas in Collaborative Session</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-members-share-chi-2026-paper-ideas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KLIC Members Share CHI 2026 Paper Ideas in Collaborative Session"/><published>2025-05-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-members-share-chi-2026-paper-ideas</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-members-share-chi-2026-paper-ideas/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/klic-members-share-chi-2026-paper-ideas.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/> On May 23, 2025, members of the Kowloon Interaction Center (KLIC) came together at the SCM Social Media Lab M7001 for a focused CHI 2026 Idea Sharing Session, marking a productive moment of reflection and forward planning following CHI 2025.</p> <p>The session featured six project ideas, each presented in a 5-minute slot. Presenters shared a range of content—from early-stage concepts to summaries of ongoing research—with the goal of receiving feedback and exploring collaboration opportunities within the group.</p> <p>After the presentations, participants engaged in open discussion, offering constructive feedback, raising insightful questions, and identifying synergies across projects. The session fostered a collegial and creative atmosphere, reinforcing KLIC’s commitment to collaborative research and early-stage idea development.</p> <p><strong>Participants included:</strong> ZHU Zihao, LIANG Minhui, Prof. ZHAO Shengdong, Aochen Jiao, Xinyu Guo, Zhang Youpeng, AP, Jussi, Zhaohui Liang, Prof. LIU Can, YANG Xuyu, Zhuangze Hou, Qianwan, Xingyu Zhou, Nuwan Janaka N P K, Qiuyuan Ren, ZHENG Xi, Jinghong Lin, Cai Runze, YAO Rui, Jingze Tian, and Prof. ZHU Kening.</p> <p>This internal session exemplifies KLIC’s collaborative spirit and its dedication to advancing HCI research through shared knowledge and mutual support. As the CHI 2026 submission cycle begins, the ideas discussed today are expected to evolve into impactful contributions.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[KLIC Members Share CHI 2026 Paper Ideas in Collaborative Session]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Prof. Joseph Jay Williams Presents on Intelligent Interventions for Behavior Change</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/prof-joseph-jay-williams-presents-on-intelligent-interventions-for-behavior-change/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Prof. Joseph Jay Williams Presents on Intelligent Interventions for Behavior Change"/><published>2025-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/prof-joseph-jay-williams-presents-on-intelligent-interventions-for-behavior-change</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/prof-joseph-jay-williams-presents-on-intelligent-interventions-for-behavior-change/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250514/prof-joseph-jay-williams-presents-on-intelligent-interventions-for-behavior-change.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/> On May 14, 2025, the <strong>Greater Bay ACM SIGCHI Chapter</strong> hosted a distinguished seminar featuring <strong>Prof. Joseph Jay Williams</strong>, Assistant Professor at the University of Toronto and Director of the Intelligent Adaptive Interventions Lab. Held at the CMC 7001 Social Media Lab, CityU, and streamed via Zoom, the event attracted a diverse audience of researchers, students, and practitioners in Human-Computer Interaction (HCI).</p> <p> </p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250514/WeChatImage_20250514154222.jpg" alt="" width="800"/> </div> <p><br/> Prof. Williams delivered a compelling talk titled <strong>“Using Adaptive Experimentation to Design Intelligent Interventions for Belief &amp; Behaviour Change.”</strong> He introduced <em>Intelligent Interventions</em>—personalized prompts, educational content, and health messages—powered by the <strong>AdaptEx framework</strong>. This innovative system integrates large language models (LLMs), crowdsourcing, and adaptive A/B testing to optimize digital interventions in real time. By transforming interface elements into learning agents, AdaptEx enables rapid experimentation and continuous improvement in user engagement and behavior change. <br/></p> <p> </p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250514/WeChatImage_20250514151409.jpg" alt="" width="800"/> </div> <p><br/> With over 85 publications and accolades including Best Paper awards and 1st place in the 1M dollars Xprize for experimentation technology, Prof. Williams’ research has impacted over 500,000 users globally. His interdisciplinary work spans computer science, psychology, statistics, and AI, supported by more than 2M dollars in research funding.</p> <p>The <strong>Greater Bay ACM SIGCHI Chapter</strong>, a network of HCI researchers across the Greater Bay Area of China, organized this event to foster knowledge exchange and collaboration. The talk exemplified their mission to connect technology, industry, and humanities through impactful HCI research.</p> <p>For more on Prof. Williams’ work, visit <a href="tiny.cc/williamspapers">tiny.cc/williamspapers</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Talk"/><category term="Greater"/><category term="Bay"/><category term="ACM"/><category term="SIGCHI"/><category term="Chapter"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prof. Joseph Jay Williams Presents on Intelligent Interventions for Behavior Change]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Successful Seminar Explores Emotion-Aware Voice Interfaces</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/successful-seminar-explores-emotion-aware-voice-interfaces/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Successful Seminar Explores Emotion-Aware Voice Interfaces"/><published>2025-05-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/successful-seminar-explores-emotion-aware-voice-interfaces</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/successful-seminar-explores-emotion-aware-voice-interfaces/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250508/successful-seminar-explores-emotion-aware-voice-interfaces.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/> On May 8th, <strong>Dr. Yong Ma</strong> from the University of Bergen delivered a seminar titled <strong>“Designing Emotion-Aware Voice Interfaces: Challenges, Insights, and Future Directions”</strong>.</p> <p>Dr. Ma explored how <em>speech signal processing</em> can be utilized to detect emotional cues and cognitive states in a non-intrusive manner. He shared findings from studies on speech emotion recognition, discussing the complexities of distinguishing between genuine and acted emotions, as well as the role of machine learning models in identifying subtle emotional differences.</p> <p>The seminar also touched upon ethical concerns, including potential biases and the broader societal impact of emotionally intelligent systems. Dr. Ma underscored the importance of user-centered design in crafting empathetic and culturally inclusive voice technologies.</p> <p>For those interested in further exploring this research, Dr. Ma’s academic contributions can be accessed <a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=CPH3qsUAAAAJ&amp;hl=en">here</a>.</p> <p>Stay tuned for more discussions on the future of human-computer interaction in upcoming events!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful Seminar Explores Emotion-Aware Voice Interfaces]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Memorable Moments—— KLIC Students &amp;amp; Faculty Shine at CHI 2025 in Yokohama 🌟</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/CHI-Moment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memorable Moments—— KLIC Students &amp;amp; Faculty Shine at CHI 2025 in Yokohama 🌟"/><published>2025-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/CHI-Moment</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/CHI-Moment/"><![CDATA[<p>This May, KLIC students and faculty came together at the prestigious CHI conference in Yokohama, Japan! 🇯🇵 From insightful discussions to sharing innovative ideas, our team made the most of this incredible opportunity. The event was filled with learning, collaboration, and of course, lots of smiles! Check out the photo to see our amazing group all in one frame.</p> <p>#CHI2025 #KLICFamily #YokohamaAdventure</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250430/1.png" alt=""/> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250430/2.jpg" alt=""/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memorable Moments—— KLIC Students & Faculty Shine at CHI 2025 in Yokohama 🌟]]></summary></entry></feed>