<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2026-02-12T00:28:37+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">KLIC Meeting Explores Practical Strategies for Better Visualizations</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/klic-meeting-explores-practical-strategies-for-better-visualizations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KLIC Meeting Explores Practical Strategies for Better Visualizations"/><published>2026-02-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-02-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/klic-meeting-explores-practical-strategies-for-better-visualizations</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/klic-meeting-explores-practical-strategies-for-better-visualizations/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20260212081042.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p>The second KLIC meeting of the semester was held on Monday, February 9, from 10:00–12:00, bringing members together for a focused discussion on improving research visuals.</p> <p>The session, titled “The Visualization Checklist: To-Dos, No-Nos, and Rules of Thumb,” shared practical strategies for designing clearer and more effective visualizations. Topics included common pitfalls, useful heuristics, and actionable tips that can be applied to academic papers, final presentations, and exploratory projects.</p> <p>The meeting took place in person at CMC 6058, with additional participants joining remotely via Zoom. The session encouraged active discussion and reflection on how thoughtful visualization choices can strengthen research communication.</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20260212081129.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second KLIC meeting of the semester was held on Monday, February 9]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Talk on Society-Centred AI by Dr. Kenny Choo</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/talk-on-society-centred-ai-by-dr-kenny-choo/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Talk on Society-Centred AI by Dr. Kenny Choo"/><published>2026-02-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-02-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/talk-on-society-centred-ai-by-dr-kenny-choo</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/talk-on-society-centred-ai-by-dr-kenny-choo/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20260206163359.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p>Dr. Kenny Choo, Assistant Professor at the Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD), delivered a talk titled “Designing for ‘We’: Expanding Collective Capability through Society-Centred AI” on February 6, 2026.</p> <p>The talk explored a shift in Human–AI Interaction from traditional user-centred approaches toward community-centred and society-centred AI. Dr. Choo shared research across multiple social scales, including multimodal systems that enhance individual expression, expert-aligned large language models supporting parent–child interactions, and AI-assisted advance care planning for complex ethical decisions. Together, these projects illustrated how AI can move beyond individual use to strengthen collective agency and social collaboration.</p> <p>The session was held in person at M6058, with additional participants joining online. The event was organized by the Greater Bay ACM SIGCHI Chapter as part of its ongoing efforts to foster research exchange and dialogue in Human–Computer Interaction.</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20260206163419.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Kenny Choo, Assistant Professor at the Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD), delivered a talk]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AI (Vibe) Coding Workshop</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/ai-vibe-coding-workshop/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AI (Vibe) Coding Workshop"/><published>2026-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/ai-vibe-coding-workshop</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/ai-vibe-coding-workshop/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20260115182651.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p>The AI (Vibe) Coding Workshop was held on Thursday, January 15, 2026, from 10:00 AM to 12:00 PM at SCM 4003, and was led by Cai Runze.</p> <p>The two-hour session introduced participants to using large language models (LLMs) as practical coding partners to support planning, code generation, and iterative development. Guided examples included creating a static personal website, building small tools to support HCI projects, and developing a simple full-stack web application with the front-end hosted on GitHub Pages and a backend using Supabase.</p> <p>The workshop provided attendees with a repeatable workflow for turning ideas into functional prototypes through AI-assisted coding.</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20260115180750.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI (Vibe) Coding Workshop was held on Thursday, January 15, 2026, from 10:00 AM to 12:00 PM at SCM 4003, and was led by Cai Runze.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bi-weekly Meeting on Behavior Change Research in HCI</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/klic-bi-weekly-meeting-on-behavior-change-research-in-hci/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bi-weekly Meeting on Behavior Change Research in HCI"/><published>2026-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-01-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/klic-bi-weekly-meeting-on-behavior-change-research-in-hci</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2026/klic-bi-weekly-meeting-on-behavior-change-research-in-hci/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20260127210605.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p>The Kowloon Interaction Design Center (KLIC) held its bi-weekly meeting on January 26, from 10:00 AM to 12:00 PM, marking the resumption of KLIC meetings for the semester.</p> <p>The session focused on Behavior Change Research in Human–Computer Interaction (HCI). The meeting covered key concepts and research methodologies in this area and included hands-on activities to support practical understanding.</p> <p>The meeting took place in person at CMC 6058, with remote access available for participants who joined online. The session was part of KLIC’s regular bi-weekly activities, which aim to support learning, discussion, and collaboration among members interested in HCI research.</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20260127210616.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[KLIC held its bi-weekly meeting on January 26, from 10:00 AM to 12:00 PM, marking the resumption of KLIC meetings for the semester.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tangible User Interfaces with Paper and Clay</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/tangible-user-interfaces-with-paper-and-clay/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tangible User Interfaces with Paper and Clay"/><published>2025-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/tangible-user-interfaces-with-paper-and-clay</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/tangible-user-interfaces-with-paper-and-clay/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20251127161905.jpg" alt="" width="70%"/></p> <p></p> <p>This week, the <strong>Kowloon Interaction Design Center (KLIC)</strong> hosted a session led by <strong>Professor Zhu Kening</strong> focused on <strong>Tangible User Interfaces (TUI)</strong>. The session explored how <strong>paper and clay</strong> can be used to create buttons and touch sensors.</p> <p>The session was designed to be <strong>hands-on</strong>, encouraging participants to engage with physical materials rather than working solely on screens. Students were invited to bring their <strong>laptops</strong>, preferably with <strong>USB Type A ports or adapters</strong>, to connect with the materials.</p> <p></p> <p><img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20251127161915.jpg" alt="" width="70%"/></p> <p></p> <p>During the session, participants experimented with making physical components function as touch-sensitive inputs, gaining practical experience in TUI design. Professor Zhu guided attendees through the process of turning everyday materials into interactive elements, providing a tangible approach to understanding user interfaces.</p> <p>This session is part of <strong>KLIC’s bi-weekly activities</strong>, which aim to create a collaborative and learning-focused environment for labs and students interested in Human–Computer Interaction.</p> <p></p> <h2 id="about-the-speaker">About the Speaker</h2> <p><strong>Professor Zhu Kening</strong> is a faculty member at the <strong>City University of Hong Kong</strong>. His research focuses on <strong>Human–Computer Interaction</strong>, particularly in the areas of tangible user interfaces, interactive design, and hands-on learning methods. Professor Zhu has led multiple workshops and sessions on physical computing and TUI, providing students with practical experience in designing interactive systems.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, KLIC hosted a hands-on session led by Professor Zhu Kening on TUI.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Anthropomorphism and Biases in Human–AI Interaction</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-seminar-anthropomorphism-and-biases-in-humanai-interaction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Anthropomorphism and Biases in Human–AI Interaction"/><published>2025-11-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-seminar-anthropomorphism-and-biases-in-humanai-interaction</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-seminar-anthropomorphism-and-biases-in-humanai-interaction/"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20251107170838.jpg" alt="" width="70%"/></p> <p>On <strong>November 6, 2025</strong>, the <strong>Kowloon Interaction Design Center (KLIC)</strong> at <strong>City University of Hong Kong</strong> hosted a seminar titled <em>“Anthropomorphism and Biases in Human–AI Interaction.”</em> The talk was delivered by <strong>Dr. Manuele Reani</strong>, <strong>Assistant Professor</strong> at the <strong>School of Management and Economics, The Chinese University of Hong Kong (Shenzhen)</strong>.</p> <p>The seminar examined how anthropomorphic design, the attribution of human-like characteristics to artificial systems, affects user perception, trust, and decision-making in interactions with AI.</p> <p></p> <p><img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20251107170831.jpg" alt="" width="70%"/></p> <p></p> <p>Dr. Reani presented findings from two complementary studies. The first introduced the <strong>Fundamental Over-Attribution Error (FOE)</strong>, a cognitive bias describing how users project human-like traits and intentions onto AI systems, particularly under risk and uncertainty. The study used multiple research methods, including experiments, surveys, and psychometric scale development, to establish FOE as a distinct construct that influences perceptions of AI reliability and intent.</p> <p>The second study explored how anthropomorphic design impacts trust and risk perception in <strong>AI-assisted decision-making</strong>, based on a large-scale experiment involving financial advisory chatbots. Results showed that anthropomorphic features reduced perceived risk by increasing both cognitive and affective trust. These effects were moderated by users’ domain expertise. Participants with lower expertise were more prone to misplaced trust, while those with higher expertise responded more critically.</p> <p>Dr. Reani concluded by discussing the implications of these findings for <strong>responsible AI design</strong>, emphasizing the importance of calibrating user trust and mitigating bias when developing anthropomorphic decision-support systems.</p> <p><strong>Time:</strong> November 6, 2025 (Thursday), 3:00–4:00 PM (BJT)<br/> <strong>Venue:</strong> SM6058, City University of Hong Kong <br/><br/><br/></p> <h3 id="about-the-speaker">About the Speaker</h3> <p></p> <p><img src="/assets/img/posts/manuele-reani.jpg" alt="Dr. Manuele Reani" width="20%"/></p> <p></p> <p>Dr. Manuele Reani is an Assistant Professor at the School of Management and Economics, The Chinese University of Hong Kong (Shenzhen). His research focuses on Human–Computer Interaction, Cognitive Science, and AI Design, with particular interest in how intelligent systems influence human cognition, trust, and decision-making.</p> <p>He holds a PhD in Computer Science from the University of Manchester, an MSc in Management Science from the London School of Economics, and a BSc in Psychology from City University London. His work has been published in leading journals and conferences including <em>IJHCS</em>, <em>Computers in Human Behavior</em>, <em>CHI</em>, and <em>CSCW</em>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 6, 2025, the Kowloon Interaction Design Center (KLIC) at City University of Hong Kong hosted a seminar titled “Anthropomorphism and Biases in Human–AI Interaction.”]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">KLIC Session Focuses on Writing the Discussion Section in HCI Papers</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/writing-the-discussion-section-in-hci-papers/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KLIC Session Focuses on Writing the Discussion Section in HCI Papers"/><published>2025-08-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/writing-the-discussion-section-in-hci-papers</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/writing-the-discussion-section-in-hci-papers/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250816104129.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p></p> <p>On Friday, August 15, 2025, KLIC held a focused session on a topic highly relevant to HCI researchers: how to write the discussion section in HCI papers. The meeting took place at 3:00 PM, with participants joining both in person at CMC 7001 and online via Zoom.</p> <p>The session aimed to support students preparing submissions for CHI and other major HCI conferences by unpacking the purpose and structure of the discussion section—a critical part of any academic paper. Participants were invited to reflect on how to effectively communicate the implications of their findings, connect results to broader research questions, and position their contributions within the field.</p> <p>To help organize the session and tailor it to attendees’ needs, students were asked to fill out a short Google form in advance. This allowed the facilitator to better understand participants’ current writing challenges and expectations.</p> <p></p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250816104116.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p></p> <p>The session encouraged open sharing and practical advice, helping students think critically about how to frame their work and engage with reviewers. While the format and specific activities were not detailed, the invitation emphasized the goal of making the session beneficial for those actively working on CHI submissions.</p> <p>This meeting reflects KLIC’s ongoing commitment to supporting student development through timely, research-focused discussions. By addressing common challenges in academic writing, KLIC continues to foster a collaborative environment where students can grow as researchers and communicators.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, August 15, 2025, KLIC held a focused session on a topic highly relevant to HCI researchers - how to write the discussion section in HCI papers.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Exploring Multimodal Interaction with Acoustophoretic Interfaces</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/exploring-multimodal-interaction-with-acoustophoretic-interfaces/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Exploring Multimodal Interaction with Acoustophoretic Interfaces"/><published>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/exploring-multimodal-interaction-with-acoustophoretic-interfaces</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/exploring-multimodal-interaction-with-acoustophoretic-interfaces/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250807202837.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p></p> <p>On August 7, 2025, KLIC hosted a session titled “Enabling Multimodal Interaction Systems with Acoustophoretic Interfaces”, featuring Dr. Lei Gao, Research Fellow at University College London.</p> <p>Dr. Gao introduced participants to acoustophoresis, or acoustic levitation—a technique that uses ultrasonic waves to manipulate objects in mid-air without physical contact. Her talk explored how acoustophoretic interfaces can generate dynamic sound fields that enable novel forms of interaction between users, digital systems, and physical environments.</p> <p>The presentation covered the technical foundations of acoustophoretic systems and showcased recent applications such as tangible data visualizations and mid-air haptic feedback, demonstrating how these technologies bridge the digital and physical worlds.</p> <p>Dr. Gao also discussed challenges in building reliable and scalable acoustophoretic interfaces and highlighted opportunities for computational solutions and interdisciplinary design. Her insights emphasized the potential of these systems to support multimodal interaction, combining visual, tactile, and spatial elements in innovative ways.</p> <h3 id="about-the-speaker">About the Speaker</h3> <p>Dr. Lei Gao is a Research Fellow in the Department of Computer Science at University College London. She earned her PhD in the Multi-Sensory Devices group led by Prof. Sriram Subramanian, where her research focused on the intersection of Human-Computer Interaction, acoustic levitation, and multisensory interfaces. Dr. Gao is particularly interested in designing novel interaction systems using ultrasonic waves and emerging technologies. She holds a master’s degree from Xidian University and a bachelor’s degree from Shandong University. Her work has been published in top venues such as CHI, SIGGRAPH, UIST, DIS, and IJHCI.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 7, 2025, KLIC hosted a session titled “Enabling Multimodal Interaction Systems with Acoustophoretic Interfaces”, featuring Dr. Lei Gao, Research Fellow at University College London.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">KLIC Hosts Engaging Session on Constructive/Artefact Research</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-engaging-session-on-constructive-artefact-research/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KLIC Hosts Engaging Session on Constructive/Artefact Research"/><published>2025-08-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-engaging-session-on-constructive-artefact-research</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-engaging-session-on-constructive-artefact-research/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/session-on-constructive-artefact-research.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p></p> <p>On August 1st, 2025, KLIC held a well-attended session titled “Introduction to Constructive/Artefact Research” at the Social Media Lab (SM7001). The event ran from 3:00 to 4:30 PM and welcomed students interested in learning about constructive research approaches and how to develop and evaluate artefacts in academic work. Stay tuned for more KLIC events coming soon!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="session"/><category term="research"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 1st, 2025, KLIC held a well-attended session titled “Introduction to Constructive/Artefact Research” at the Social Media Lab (SM7001).]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">KLIC Hosts Collaborative Visit to Microsoft Research Asia in Hong Kong</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-collaborative-visit-to-microsoft-research-asia-in-hong-kong/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KLIC Hosts Collaborative Visit to Microsoft Research Asia in Hong Kong"/><published>2025-06-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-collaborative-visit-to-microsoft-research-asia-in-hong-kong</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-hosts-collaborative-visit-to-microsoft-research-asia-in-hong-kong/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624201033.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> On June 24, 2025, KLIC organized a collaborative visit to Microsoft Research Asia (MSRA) in Hong Kong, bringing together researchers, faculty, and students from City University of Hong Kong and MSRA for an afternoon of academic exchange and networking. <p><p/> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200442.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> The event began at 2:00 PM with a welcome speech by hosts Yan and Shengdong, followed by an overview of MSRA’s research direction, team structure, and institutional positioning, presented by Shujie and Yun. <p><p/> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200651.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200839.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200853.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> From 2:30 PM to 3:00 PM, Andong and Dingdong presented two ongoing research projects at MSRA Hong Kong, highlighting innovative approaches and recent findings. Their talks sparked engaging discussions and set the tone for deeper collaboration. <p><p/> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200124.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/Image_20250624200612.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><p/> Between 3:00 PM and 4:00 PM, representatives from CityU—including both faculty and students—shared their current research interests, challenges, and ideas for potential partnerships. This flexible session encouraged open dialogue and mutual learning. The visit continued with a guided tour of MSRA’s office space, offering guests a behind-the-scenes look at the institute’s working environment. The day concluded with a group photo session at 5:00 PM, marking the end of a productive and inspiring visit. This exchange not only strengthened ties between CityU and MSRA but also opened doors for future collaboration in HCI and related fields. </p></p></p></p></p></p></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="session"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 24, 2025, KLIC organized a collaborative visit to Microsoft Research Asia (MSRA) in Hong Kong, bringing together researchers, faculty, and students from City University of Hong Kong and MSRA for an afternoon of academic exchange and networking.]]></summary></entry></feed>