<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-06-04T03:10:41+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">MSRA Team Joins Student Presentation and Feedback Session</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/msra-team-joins-student-presentation-and-feedback-session/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MSRA Team Joins Student Presentation and Feedback Session"/><published>2025-06-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-06-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/msra-team-joins-student-presentation-and-feedback-session</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/msra-team-joins-student-presentation-and-feedback-session/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20250604105015.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/> A group from Microsoft Research Asia (MSRA) recently joined a session featuring student presentations and feedback exchange. The event provided an opportunity for students to share their work and receive comments from experienced professionals in the field.</p> <p><strong>The MSRA attendees included:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Lily Sun, Director of the MSRA Accelerator Team</li> <li>Shujie Liu, Principal Researcher</li> <li>Beibei Shi, Principal Research Program Manager</li> <li>Jinglu Wang, Senior Researcher</li> <li>Yun Wang, Senior Researcher</li> </ul> <p>During the session, several students presented their research ideas and ongoing projects. The MSRA visitors offered feedback, contributing their perspectives and engaging with the presenters.</p> <p>The session served as a valuable platform for interaction between students and researchers, encouraging thoughtful discussion and reflection. KLIC appreciates the participation of the MSRA team and the time they dedicated to engaging with the student work.</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/Image_20250604105008.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSRA Team Joins Student Presentation and Feedback Session]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">KLIC Members Share CHI 2026 Paper Ideas in Collaborative Session</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-members-share-chi-2026-paper-ideas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="KLIC Members Share CHI 2026 Paper Ideas in Collaborative Session"/><published>2025-05-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-members-share-chi-2026-paper-ideas</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/klic-members-share-chi-2026-paper-ideas/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/klic-members-share-chi-2026-paper-ideas.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/> On May 23, 2025, members of the Kowloon Interaction Center (KLIC) came together at the SCM Social Media Lab M7001 for a focused CHI 2026 Idea Sharing Session, marking a productive moment of reflection and forward planning following CHI 2025.</p> <p>The session featured six project ideas, each presented in a 5-minute slot. Presenters shared a range of content—from early-stage concepts to summaries of ongoing research—with the goal of receiving feedback and exploring collaboration opportunities within the group.</p> <p>After the presentations, participants engaged in open discussion, offering constructive feedback, raising insightful questions, and identifying synergies across projects. The session fostered a collegial and creative atmosphere, reinforcing KLIC’s commitment to collaborative research and early-stage idea development.</p> <p><strong>Participants included:</strong> ZHU Zihao, LIANG Minhui, Prof. ZHAO Shengdong, Aochen Jiao, Xinyu Guo, Zhang Youpeng, AP, Jussi, Zhaohui Liang, Prof. LIU Can, YANG Xuyu, Zhuangze Hou, Qianwan, Xingyu Zhou, Nuwan Janaka N P K, Qiuyuan Ren, ZHENG Xi, Jinghong Lin, Cai Runze, YAO Rui, Jingze Tian, and Prof. ZHU Kening.</p> <p>This internal session exemplifies KLIC’s collaborative spirit and its dedication to advancing HCI research through shared knowledge and mutual support. As the CHI 2026 submission cycle begins, the ideas discussed today are expected to evolve into impactful contributions.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[KLIC Members Share CHI 2026 Paper Ideas in Collaborative Session]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Prof. Joseph Jay Williams Presents on Intelligent Interventions for Behavior Change</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/prof-joseph-jay-williams-presents-on-intelligent-interventions-for-behavior-change/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Prof. Joseph Jay Williams Presents on Intelligent Interventions for Behavior Change"/><published>2025-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/prof-joseph-jay-williams-presents-on-intelligent-interventions-for-behavior-change</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/prof-joseph-jay-williams-presents-on-intelligent-interventions-for-behavior-change/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250514/prof-joseph-jay-williams-presents-on-intelligent-interventions-for-behavior-change.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/> On May 14, 2025, the <strong>Greater Bay ACM SIGCHI Chapter</strong> hosted a distinguished seminar featuring <strong>Prof. Joseph Jay Williams</strong>, Assistant Professor at the University of Toronto and Director of the Intelligent Adaptive Interventions Lab. Held at the CMC 7001 Social Media Lab, CityU, and streamed via Zoom, the event attracted a diverse audience of researchers, students, and practitioners in Human-Computer Interaction (HCI).</p> <p> </p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250514/WeChatImage_20250514154222.jpg" alt="" width="800"/> </div> <p><br/> Prof. Williams delivered a compelling talk titled <strong>“Using Adaptive Experimentation to Design Intelligent Interventions for Belief &amp; Behaviour Change.”</strong> He introduced <em>Intelligent Interventions</em>—personalized prompts, educational content, and health messages—powered by the <strong>AdaptEx framework</strong>. This innovative system integrates large language models (LLMs), crowdsourcing, and adaptive A/B testing to optimize digital interventions in real time. By transforming interface elements into learning agents, AdaptEx enables rapid experimentation and continuous improvement in user engagement and behavior change. <br/></p> <p> </p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250514/WeChatImage_20250514151409.jpg" alt="" width="800"/> </div> <p><br/> With over 85 publications and accolades including Best Paper awards and 1st place in the 1M dollars Xprize for experimentation technology, Prof. Williams’ research has impacted over 500,000 users globally. His interdisciplinary work spans computer science, psychology, statistics, and AI, supported by more than 2M dollars in research funding.</p> <p>The <strong>Greater Bay ACM SIGCHI Chapter</strong>, a network of HCI researchers across the Greater Bay Area of China, organized this event to foster knowledge exchange and collaboration. The talk exemplified their mission to connect technology, industry, and humanities through impactful HCI research.</p> <p>For more on Prof. Williams’ work, visit <a href="tiny.cc/williamspapers">tiny.cc/williamspapers</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Talk"/><category term="Greater"/><category term="Bay"/><category term="ACM"/><category term="SIGCHI"/><category term="Chapter"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prof. Joseph Jay Williams Presents on Intelligent Interventions for Behavior Change]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Successful Seminar Explores Emotion-Aware Voice Interfaces</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/successful-seminar-explores-emotion-aware-voice-interfaces/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Successful Seminar Explores Emotion-Aware Voice Interfaces"/><published>2025-05-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-05-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/successful-seminar-explores-emotion-aware-voice-interfaces</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/successful-seminar-explores-emotion-aware-voice-interfaces/"><![CDATA[<div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250508/successful-seminar-explores-emotion-aware-voice-interfaces.jpg" alt="" width="1000"/> </div> <p><br/> On May 8th, <strong>Dr. Yong Ma</strong> from the University of Bergen delivered a seminar titled <strong>“Designing Emotion-Aware Voice Interfaces: Challenges, Insights, and Future Directions”</strong>.</p> <p>Dr. Ma explored how <em>speech signal processing</em> can be utilized to detect emotional cues and cognitive states in a non-intrusive manner. He shared findings from studies on speech emotion recognition, discussing the complexities of distinguishing between genuine and acted emotions, as well as the role of machine learning models in identifying subtle emotional differences.</p> <p>The seminar also touched upon ethical concerns, including potential biases and the broader societal impact of emotionally intelligent systems. Dr. Ma underscored the importance of user-centered design in crafting empathetic and culturally inclusive voice technologies.</p> <p>For those interested in further exploring this research, Dr. Ma’s academic contributions can be accessed <a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=CPH3qsUAAAAJ&amp;hl=en">here</a>.</p> <p>Stay tuned for more discussions on the future of human-computer interaction in upcoming events!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful Seminar Explores Emotion-Aware Voice Interfaces]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Memorable Moments—— KLIC Students &amp;amp; Faculty Shine at CHI 2025 in Yokohama 🌟</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/CHI-Moment/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memorable Moments—— KLIC Students &amp;amp; Faculty Shine at CHI 2025 in Yokohama 🌟"/><published>2025-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/CHI-Moment</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2025/CHI-Moment/"><![CDATA[<p>This May, KLIC students and faculty came together at the prestigious CHI conference in Yokohama, Japan! 🇯🇵 From insightful discussions to sharing innovative ideas, our team made the most of this incredible opportunity. The event was filled with learning, collaboration, and of course, lots of smiles! Check out the photo to see our amazing group all in one frame.</p> <p>#CHI2025 #KLICFamily #YokohamaAdventure</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250430/1.png" alt=""/> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20250430/2.jpg" alt=""/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memorable Moments—— KLIC Students & Faculty Shine at CHI 2025 in Yokohama 🌟]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Successful KLIC Retreat Facilitates Collaboration and Knowledge Exchange</title><link href="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2024/KLIC-Retreat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Successful KLIC Retreat Facilitates Collaboration and Knowledge Exchange"/><published>2024-03-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2024/KLIC-Retreat</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sszhao74.github.io/blog/2024/KLIC-Retreat/"><![CDATA[<p>Last weekend, on March 23rd and 24th, the Synteraction Lab hosted a successful KLIC retreat aimed at fostering collaboration and knowledge exchange among students.</p> <p>The KLIC (Kowloon Interaction Center) retreat brought together students focusing on HCI at City University of Hong Kong. The event, spanning two days, served as a platform for participants to build relationships, promote interdisciplinary collaboration, and establish KLIC as a hub for interaction.</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20240329/2.jpg" alt=""/> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20240329/3.jpg" alt=""/> </div> <p>The first day of the retreat was dedicated to introductions and acquaintances, allowing attendees to get to know each other and lay the foundation for future collaborations. On the second day, discussions and planning sessions were held.</p> <div class="post_img"> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20240329/4.jpg" alt=""/> <img src="/assets/img/posts/20240329/5.jpg" alt=""/> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Successful KLIC Retreat Facilitates Collaboration and Knowledge Exchange]]></summary></entry></feed>